你好，漂亮的人欢迎你们来这一节课程。
Hello you beautiful people are welcome to this section of the course.
所有关于如何在Linux计算机上安装和管理软件的内容。
All about how to install and manage software on a Linux computer.
现在Linux是一个开放源码的操作系统，其中最棒的一点是
Now Linux is an open source operating system and the great thing about that is that there are around
世界上数以百万计的软件开发人员正在创建软件和各种奇妙的
the world millions and millions of software developers who are creating software and all kinds of fantastic
并免费提供给人们下载。
stuff and making it available for free for people to download.
这是相当酷的，这意味着我们可以从中获益一点点。
So that's pretty cool that means we can benefit from that a little bit.
现在，Lilek有一些令人惊叹的方法可以让您访问该软件。
Now Lileks has some amazing ways for you to gain access to this software.
我的意思是这一节我要教你怎么做。
I mean this section I'm going to show you how to do it.
因此，在这一节中，您将从很多开源的实际含义开始。
So in the section you're going to start off with a lot of what Open-Source actually means.
您是否打算向您展示我们将如何查看某些命令的实际源代码，这些命令
Are you going to show we're going to show you how you can see actual source code for some commands that
您已经在本课程中看到过，然后您将学习如何使用软件存储库进行搜索
you've already seen in the course and then you'll learn how to use the software repositories to search
用于并安装新软件。
for and install new software.
保持该软件为最新版本，并在不再需要时将其删除。
Keep that software up to date and also had to remove it when you no longer need it.
因此，我们将向您展示整个包。
So we're going to show you the whole package.
现在，通常在谈论Linux课程上的软件管理时，只需告诉您以下命令
Now usually when talking about software management on Linux courses just tell you into this command
这个命令和这个命令与Union一起使用，您只需要记住它，这是很有用的，而且除了
and this command and this command with union you just got to memorize it which is useful and all but
它从来不会让你真正知道它背后的意思，也不会让你觉得你真的明白了
it never really shows you you know the meaning behind it or leaves you feeling like you actually understand
您在做什么，以及为什么要使用某个命令。
what you're doing and why you're using a certain command.
因此，在本节中，您不仅将了解要运行哪些命令，还将了解如何
So in this section you're not only going to understand what commands to run you're also understand how
您的软件经理正在暗中工作，帮助您在中安装、更新和管理软件
your software manager is working under the hood to help you install update and manage software in your
新的Linux系统。
new Linux system.
因此，在这一节结束时，您将对软件有一个非常深入和实用的理解
So by the end of the section you have a wonderfully in-depth and practical understanding of software
经理和你也有实际的知识，如何得到比你能玩的更多闪亮的新玩具。
managers and you also have the practical know how to get more shiny new toys to play with than you can
可以想象。
possibly imagine.
所以，对于所有的好东西，我会在下一个视频中见到你。
So for all the good stuff I'll see you in the next video.